# **Gregory Blood**

Website: gregoryblood.github.io

1115 SW 26th St. Corvallis, Oregon, 97333 (702) 606-7433 gregoryblood1998@gmail.com

## **Career Objective**

Versatile programmer with experience in both low-level and high-level languages with knowledge in OOP, data structures, and computer networking. I want to combine my creativity with efficiency while working in a team to satisfy given tasks. I believe my attention to detail and analytical thinking will be valuable for your business.

## **Technical Proficiencies**

### **Education**

**Oregon State University** - Corvallis, OR (2017-Present)

**Bachelor of Computer Science** 

Straight A's in all CS courses. Some of these classes include:

Data Structures – Computer Architecture and Assembly – Web Development – Computer
Networking – Software Engineering

### **Experience**

## **Data Structure Teacher Assistant** - Corvallis, OR (2019-Present)

Working with a professor, I held office hours to help students with data structures along with reviewing and grading their projects. I also proctored and graded quizzes for 30+ students.

## Canvassing - Corvallis, OR (2018-2018)

Working with a team members, I determined how to efficiently split up territory to talk with diverse people. I learned the value of communicating clearly to figure what information people wanted to know.

## **Projects**

# My Website - HTML5, CSS3, Javascript - gregoryblood.github.io

To create this site, I compared it to a sales pitch. It had to be pleasant and enticing, while at the same time clearly communicating my information quickly. I began creating blueprints of the design and modeled it after the popular Monokai theme so many programmers use.

# WhatToWear - HTML5, CSS3, Javascript - gregoryblood.github.io/weatherapi

I check the weather every morning to figure out what to wear but I always forget what a temperature actually feels like. So I created a site that uses DarkSky.net's API and the device's location to display as clearly as possible, what kind of clothes to wear, and 'weather' you need an umbrella or a raincoat.

Check out my website for more projects and information